NARRATOR: Kids, you never know when you're about to meet someone reallymportant.
孩儿们 你们永远不会知道缘分何时降临
It's not like life gives you  a warnin
老天爷可不会给你提个醒儿
You just look up  d there they are.
只是一抬头 她便在眼前
Come on, we're going to go get trashed on the roof.
来吧 我们一起到天台上一醉方休
, not that dude.
不是那哥们
Her.
是她
I'm good, Boomer.
不用了 Boomer (电脑游戏中的变异人类)
My name's not Boomer.
我不叫Boomer
Oh, in my he, it is.
我记得是
Gentlemen,I'm a facultmember, and you're underage,
先生 我是老师 你们还未成年
so it's my duty to confiscate this and this and--
所以我要没收这个 这个还有
hard lemonade?
柠檬汽酒?
You know what, Boomer?You can keep that.
Boomer 你就留着吧
I swear,every week I get asked by some frat guy to a kegger,
我发誓 每周兄弟会的男生 请我参加啤酒聚会
and I say,
我都会说
"I'm a PhD candidate writing dissertation entitled
我是博士生 正在写名为
'Foreign Direct Investment and Intergenerational Linkages in Consumpon Behavior.'"
"外来直接投资与 两代人之间消费行为的联系"的论文
And what does Frat Guy say to that?
兄弟会的男生什么反应?
: "That's hot."
真火辣
Actually, that is kind of hot.
确实有点火辣
Ted, I have a confession.
Ted 我得坦白一点
I recognize you.
我认识你
Do you remembethe first day of classes last semester?Econ 305?
还记得上学期的第一堂课吗? 经济学305室?
Kids, you remember  the wrong classroom story.
孩儿们 我跑错教室的那次 你们还记得吧
I thought I was in Ahitecture  101, but it was Econ 305.
我以为是建筑学101室 其实是经济学305室
Of course,  what I didt know was that your mother was  somewhere in that clas
当然 我不知道你们老妈也上那堂课
and she though  I was a complete idiot.
她觉得我蠢到家了
I thought you were a complete idiot.
我觉得你蠢到家了
But a very cute idiot.
但傻得可爱
So, um, do you ever date cute idiots?
那你和可爱的小白约会过吗?
Almost exclusively.
几乎都是
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=-
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品  本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 花竹梗 HOLAH 校对: 葱家的小毛毛 Grace 时间轴: 泡泡飞
How.I.Met.Your.Mother
老爸老妈浪漫史 第五季 第12集
She's a PhD candidate,
她是博士生
she reads philosophy for fun,
她读哲学仅仅是因为好玩
she does the Sunday crossword every week and finishes it.
每周都做填词游戏而且都通关了
Ted, I am so happy for you―
Ted 真为你高兴
sorry,not for you, happy I'm not you.
抱歉 不是为你 真高兴我不是你
Long story short: I have a date tonight.
长话短说 我今晚要去约会
Thanks, New York, I'll try not to screw it up.
谢谢 纽约 我不会搞砸的
What's going on?There's a huge line outside MacLaren's.
咋回事? MacLaren酒吧外排起了长龙
And why ist almost relyenti dudes?
为啥清一色都是男的?
Only two things could cause that kind of commotion.
只有两个东东能导致这样的骚动
Boobs.
咪咪们
* She's my cherry pie... *
* 她是我的樱桃派 *
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士们先生们
MacLaren's h hired a hot bartender.
MacLaren酒吧雇了一个火辣的酒保
Look aall these guys.
瞅瞅这些人
The sidewalk's going to smell like pee-pee now.
人行道上要尿味满天飘了
我们最好重新找家酒吧
What, are you-- what, are you-- aryou crazy?
啥 啥 你们脑抽吗?
It is a hot bartder.
这么热辣的酒保
Do younow how long I have been waiting to land a...
你们知道我多么想泡...
My friends, have been with many women in my day.
我的朋友 我的一生 泡过N多妞
Lawyers, teachers, poets, doctors,
律师 教师 诗人 医生
professional equestrians, amateur equestrians...
专业马术骑手 业余马术骑手
A butcher, a baker, a candlestick maker--
屠夫 面包师 烛台工人
yes,e're to the rhyming section now--
对 我们现在进入押韵部分
a math professor, a tax asseor, a weight guesser...
数学教员 估税员  体重猜测员
A puppeteer,
木偶戏演员
a blackjack dealer,
21点的发牌员
a stay-at-homeom-- that's a job, too, guys--
家庭主妇 那也是一种职业
- a circuit court judge...
- 巡回法庭的法官 - 别绕弯子!
I have never, ever scored a hot bartender
有生以来我从没泡过热辣的酒保
until tonight.
今晚将突破历史
She's really not that hot.
她真没那么性感
Aw, is someone jealous of all the attention?
某人嫉妒了?
Did somebody fancy herself the hottest girl in the ba
某人自认为是酒吧里的性感女神?
Gosh, no. Shut up!
天哪 才没 闭嘴!
All right, wish me luck.
好吧 祝我好运
All right, it'sever going to happen.
不会成功的
Barney, she's just going to pretend to like you
Barney 她会假装喜欢你
the same way she hypnotized all these geniuses
就跟忽悠那些天才一样
Yeah, but guess who's nogoing to fall under her spell?
嗯 但我不会拜倒在她的裙摆下
I'm goa be all, "Drop the act, baby doll.Daddy needs a gin and tonic."
我会说"表装了 洋娃娃 老爹要杜松子酒加奎宁水"
I'm gonna just spit it out and say, "Try again."
然后全吐出来说"再调一杯"
Boom! Alpha dog is right where he belongs:on top,
嘣! 姜还是老的辣
then after a feminutes, on the bottom.Why should I do all the work?
用不了多久就能爽歪歪 我这么费劲为嘛?
Hi, Marshall. Guys, what's happening?
- 嗨 Marshall - 伙计们 咋了?
New superhot bartender.
辣到爆的新酒保
Ha, ha, see?Marshall doesn't think she's hot either.
哈? 瞧 Marshall也不觉得她火辣
Yes, he does.
不是
Baby, you don't have to pretend other women aren't aractive just for my sake.
宝贝 你没必要为了我 假装其他女人毫无魅力
I know, and if that woman were anywhere near as hot as the woman I'm married to,
我知道 要是她 能有我老婆那么性感
th I'd admit it,but she's not.
那我会承认 但她比不上
Oh, baby, you're so sweet, but compared to that woman,
宝贝 你真好 但和那女人比起来
I am a big bag of three-day-old garbage.
我就像是堆积三天的垃圾袋
Well, I call 'em like I se'em, and...
我是实事求是
I just think you're the most beautiful woman in the world.
我觉得你是世界上最美的女人
See, that's just annoying.
看见了吧 这样真讨厌
Oh, my God, you are so fny.
我的天 你真风趣
That'll be $6.75.
6.75块
Here's a 50, keep t change.
给你50 不用找了
Oh, thank you.
谢谢
Amateurs.
真外行
What do you want?
你要什么?
Drop the act, baby doll--wait, wh?
表装了 洋娃娃 等下 啥?
Are you gonna order a drink or are you jusgonna stand there looking stupid?
你要点酒还是继续傻愣在这?
I don'know how to make an um.
我不知道怎么办
Is that equal parts vodka and get-the-hell-out-of-my face?
倒点伏特加外加一脚把你踹走?
Hey, Bobby!What's going on?
嘿 Bobby! 要点什么?
Later that night, I embarked upon a very important  first date.
那天晚上 我开始了 至关重要的第一次约会
- How are you? - Good. Come in.
- 你好吗? - 很好 进来吧
It's funny,  sometimes you walk into a place you've never been before,
很有意思 有时你走进 一处未曾到过的地方
but you get the feing you're exactly  where you're supposed to be.
但你却有似曾相识之感
And kids, that's the first time  I ever saw your mother's  little yellow bus.
孩儿们 那是我第一次看见 你们老妈的黄色小公交车
You know the one.
你们知道的
It's right behind you.
就在你们身后
Hey, this is cute.
嘿 真可爱
其实是我室友的
3333 as, kids, standing  in your ther's apartment,
孩儿们 那时我就在你们老妈的公寓里
Ner mind the fact that I was  on a date with her roommate Cindy.
别介意我正和她的室友Cindy约会
Sorry, I shoul't be messing with your roomte's stuff.
抱歉 我不该乱动你室友的东西
What's she like?
她人怎么样?
I didn't know it,  but I was about to hear
接下来我要听到的是 他人对日后与我共结连理的
the very first description  of the woman I'd one day marry.
女人的首次描述 对此我毫不知情
She's a whore.
她是个婊子
- I think she's a dominatrix. - What?
- 我觉得她是个母夜叉 - 什么?
Okay, I'm sorry, none of that is true.
好吧 抱歉 那些都是假话
I have a bit of aoommate complex.
我有点讨厌她
Why?
为什么?
Guys arelways falling in love with her.
男生老是会爱上她
Hey, hey, look at me.
嘿 嘿 看着我
I promise you I am not going to fall in love with your roommate.
我向你保证我不会爱上你室友
Oops.
啊呃
Okay, now that you've had closer look, admit it:
好吧 现在你近距离看过了 就承认吧
That bartender is the hottest woman in this bar.
那酒保是这酒吧里最性感的妞
: Second hottest.
第二性感的
I repeat...
我重申一遍
Baby, how cod you not want to hit that?
宝贝 你怎么会不想泡她?
I want to hit that.
我都想泡
you don't want to hit that,I'm sorry, but you might be gay.
你若不想泡她 抱歉你可能是基
Hell, yeah, I'm gay.
是啊 我是基
Gay for u.
你的专属基
Whatever. Did you find out why
随便啦 你打听到为啥
I'm the one guy in this entire bar she seems to despise?
整个酒吧里她最鄙视我了吗?
I did, um...
打听到了
You're not going to like the answer.
你不会想知道答案的
(2 mintues ago) My last the boyfriends were Wall Street guys--
(2分钟前) 我最后3个男友都是华尔街男
bastards--so I vowed neveagain to date a guy who wears suits.
混蛋 我发誓再也 不和西装革履的男人约会了
Okay, well, that's easy.All I have to do is stop wearing suits
那好 简单得很 我只要不穿西装
that's all, Barney?Come on, you're never not in a suit.
就这么着了 Barney? 拜托 西装是你的命根
2009年夏天
True... but for those--I mean, fo
没错 但为了那些(咪咪们) 我是说为了那个(胸部)
I mean, for her...
我是说 为了她
I will stop wearing--
我要脱下
- wait for it... - We know you're going to say "suits."
- 等下... - 我们知道你要说"西装"
...suits.
西装
Meanwhile, Cindy and I were having a lovely evening,
与此同时 我和Cindy正在享受美妙的夜晚
except she wasn't kidding  about her roommate complex.
除了她对室友的症结并非是说着玩玩
And another weird thing about my roommate:
还有一件我室友干的怪事
She does these bizarre paintings of robots playing sports.
她尽画些机器人玩竞技体育的怪画
Yeah, that is weird.
嗯 真怪胎
I was lying. That snded awesome.
我说谎了 真是帅呆了
Your mother's Robot Volleyball watercolor  is hanging up  in the den as we speak.
我们说话的当口 你们老妈的水彩画 "机器人打排球"正挂在书房里
Yeah,and she has this cra habit of making breakfast food sing show tunes.
嗯 她还喜欢让早餐唱音乐剧
That's just bizarre.
真荒唐
Your mother's rendition  of "Memories"
你们老妈用英式松饼
as performed by an  English muffin is, to this day,
演奏的"Memories" 时至今日
the most hauntingly beautiful  thing ve ever heard.
是我听到过的最难忘的美妙音乐
Look, I'm sold.
听着 我被同化了
I hate this girl.
我讨厌这姑娘
I'm sorry.Look, she's not that bad.
抱歉 听着 她也不是那么糟
I just get a little jealous.
我只是有点嫉妒
don't know why.
为什么啊
You' awesome.
你很棒
But not as awesome  as your mother.
但是和你们老妈没法比
And speaking of things  th are less awesome,
谈到那些不尽如人意的事
your Uncle Barney had officially suited down.
你们的Barney叔叔正式把西装脱下了
I am so sorry I misjudged you.
真对不起我错看你了
If there is one type of person that I cannot stand,
如果说有一类人我无法忍受
it is a man in a suit.
那就是西装革履的男人
That and a woman who has no respect for herself.
还有缺乏自尊的女人
Suits and insecure women-- I hate 'em.
西装和水性杨花的女人 真讨厌
Just hate 'em.
就是讨厌
Hey, how was your date withindy?
嘿 你和Cindy的约会怎么样?
Well, last night was great, today not so much.
昨晚很好 今天不太好
What, why?
啥 为啥?
I found out thschool's policy about students and professors dating is really strict.
我发现限制学生和教授约会的校规 很严格
I could lose my scholarship.
我可能会丢了奖学金
Yeah, but i-it's not like you're in my class.
嗯 但你不上我的课
I mean, we're not even in the same department.
我是说 我们压根不是一个系的
I'm sorry, but I just can't risk it.
对不起 我不能冒这个险
She's completely overreacting, right?
她反应过头了 对吧?
Actually, Ted, she has a point.
其实 Ted 她说得也有道理
LILY: Yeah, and think about it.If the rules are that strict,
嗯 仔细想想 要是校规真这么严格
you could be putting ur job in jeopardy.
你可能会丢饭碗
I think, I think you got to let this one go, buddy.
我觉得你放她走吧 哥们
Let's try this again:she's completely overreacting, right?
我们再来一遍  她反应过头了 对吧?
Of course, they were right.
当然 他们说得对
I had to let it go,
我只得放手
but as your Uncle Barney  was about to find out,
不过你们的Barney叔叔发现
it's not seasy  to let things go.
放手何其不易
:  Suit u
穿西装
NARRATOR:  Now, none  us had ever seen Barney gthis long  without suiting up,
我们谁也没有见过Barney 那么久不穿西装
and kids, it wasn't pretty.
孩儿们 这不太妙
So sorry I'm late.
真抱歉迟到了
I got stuck at work.
我忙着工作 跑不开
You know how today I had that presentation on offshore dividend tax plications?
你们知道我今天关于 境外分红税的演讲做得咋样吗?
Sure, I was totally paying attention wh you talked about that.
是呀~ 我之前有听你说过 (其实根本就忘记了)
Right, so I fire up the PowerPoint...
然后我打开PPT...
Um, Barney?
Barney?
Barney.
Barney
:  Suit up.*
西装快上身~
MARSHALL: Hey, Barney, we're going to order se food.
Barney 我们要点菜了
Okay, be o in a sec.
好好 我就来
No.
不...
Out of the way!
别挡道!
Stay with me.It's not your time.
振作点 你能行的
NARRATOR:  If anyone could fix something  like this,
若说有人能修补好这样的意外
it was Barney's  personal tailor,
那就非Barney的私人裁缝莫属了
TV's Tim Gunn.
大名鼎鼎的Tim Gunn (天桥骄子主持人 著名设计师)
I'm sorry, Barney.I couldn't make it work.
很遗憾 Barney 我也无能为力了
So young.
它还那么年轻
There's nothing else you could do?
难道就没有其他办法了吗?
No, but there is another suit that can use the buttons from your su.
没有 但你那套西装的纽扣 能用在其他西装上
That can...Like an organ donor?
那可以...就像器官捐赠那样?
Your suit's death could mean another suit's life.
你的西装之死能成全其他西装的性命
But I...
可我...
Do it.
放手做吧
You're doing the right thing.
这是正确的选择
Please don't cry on this.
请别哭湿了这套衣服
- It's silk. - I'm sorry.
- 这是丝绸做的 - 对不起
We cremated the remains.
他的遗体被火化了
His butts saved the life of a sick little jacketon the Upper
而他的纽扣挽救了 上东区一件小夹克的性命
Well, at least now you can finalldrop this quest for the so-called Hot Bartender.
至少这个所谓火辣酒保的任务 能告一段落了
No.
不
My suit gave its life for this cause,
我的西装因此而献出生命
and I will not rest until those...
我不会停息 直到那双...
I mean, at...I mean, she... is mine.
不对 那个... 不对 她...落入我怀抱
He's absolutely right.
他说的不错
Who, the guy kissing a jar fl of dead suit ashes-- that guy?
谁? 刚刚亲吻西装骨灰罐的人--就他?
What if Cindy is the woman I'm supposedo marry,and m just giving up?
万一Cindy真的是我命中注定的人 而我却放弃了怎么办?
So long, elegant, yet welcoming me in Westchester
我就跟Westchester高雅别致 还等着我的家永别了
with a sensible mortgage I can handle wiout dipping into my savings.
它按揭合理 能轻易负担  不需我动用积蓄
Bye-bye, two kids I raised with a stern, yet loving hd,
再见吧 在我表面严厉 实质爱护的管教下 成长的俩孩子
finding the perfect balance between father and friend.
我们亦父亦友 其乐融融
Adios, triplet schnauzers, Frank, Lloyd and Wright.
别了 三胞胎雪纳瑞 Frank Lloyd 和Wright
Ted! Ted! Ted!
Thpoint is,I'm not giving up, either!
关键是 我也不会放弃!
I don't know why I just did that.
天知道我为啥会这么做
Barney, I'm so sorry about your friend.
Barney 你朋友的事我很遗憾
Tell me about him.
说说他吧
Heas Italian.
他是意大利人
Classy, elegant.
格调高雅
And boy, did he have a way with the ladies.
还有 真不知道他是不是对女性下了咒
They just couldn't say no.
那些女的都不能抗拒他
- How old was he? - Seven.
- 他多大了? - 七岁
I miss him so much!
我真想念他!
You shouldn't be alone tonight.
今晚你不会寂寞
I'm gonna end my shift early.
今晚我提早下班
Thank you, old friend.
感谢你 老朋友
: You're going out with a bang.
我要以嘿咻祭拜你
LILY: Come on, Marshall.Just admit that she's hotter than me.
别这样 Marshall 承认吧 她比我辣
I won't be hurt.
我不介意
Can't do it.You're hotter.
恕难从命 你比较辣
Oh, she's a goddess!
她简直是女神!
Her skin glows.Her legs gfor miles.
她皮肤这么光滑 双腿如此修长
And that a?I would wear that thing for a hat.
还有那小屁屁?  翘得都能戴在头上当帽子了
Last night in bed, I'll admit it,
昨晚在床上 我承认
she popped into  head a couple of times.
她在我的幻想里盘桓了一阵
Whoa, wh, whoa. What are you try...?
你你你...?
Like, you think she's hotter than me?
你是说你觉得她比我辣?
I never said that.
我没这么说过
MARSHALL: Oh, my God!You do.
苍天呐! 你真的这么想
It's apples and orans.She's younger than you.
这是鱼与熊掌的问题 可她比你年轻
I'm just saying, like,me in  prime versus her in her prime.
那...那就拿各自的优点比较一下
Oh, my God!You guys, her hotness isn't even real!
受不了你们了! 她根本没那么性感
It's circumstantial hotness.
那只是环境影响而已
Watch.
看着
* She's my cherry pie
* Cool drink of water, such a sweet surprise *
* Taste so good, ke a grown man cry... *
I-I suppose you think she's hotter than me, too.
我看你会觉得连她都比我辣了
What the hell are you doing?! What?
- 你在干嘛?!  - 什么?
You're not allowed back here.
你不可以就这么闯进来的
Oh, no. Uh, I... Carl, look.
我... Carl 是这样的
No. I-I don't want to go back.
我-我不想走
Please, please, don't make me go back.
拜托 拜托 别把我打回原形
- You got to go.
你不能在这里
No, Carl. I was... I was somebody back there!
别 Carl 我在那里可是大人物!
Everybody loved me
大家都喜欢我
Can we talk?
能聊一下吗?
My roommate's just about to get out of the shower.
我室友快洗完澡了
Let's talk in my room.
进我房间聊吧
Look, Cindy, I kno the University Rulebook says we can't date.
Cindy 我了解 大学里规定我们不能约会
But it also says, "Don't teach drunk,"
但也有规定 "不能酒后授课"
and I do that all the time.
而我每次都这么做
The point is,I ke you.
我想说 我喜欢你
I do.You'reweet, you're funny.
真的 你既可爱又风趣
entitled, Foreign Direct Invesent and Intergenerational Linkages  and Consumption Behavior.
你写的论文叫
I mean, that is hot.
那真是性感
I know this soun crazy, but...
我知道这听起来挺疯狂 但是...
I feel like our path are supposed to cross somehow.
我知道我们的人生肯定会有所交集
And I don't want to miss out on knowing you.
我就是不想错过深入了解你的机会
I don't want to miss out on knowing you, either.
我也不想错过深入了解你
Look, I got to tell you,
我得说
I mean, just from oking around your room,I n tell we have a ton in common.
光是看着你的房间 我敢说我们有许多共同点
Really?
真的?
The Unicor? Who Will Cut Our Hair  When We're Gone?
独角兽乐队的
I have never met anyone else who has this album.
我没见过其他人有这张专辑
That's my roomte's. I borrowed it.
那是我室友的 我借她的
Well, well, what about this?
还有这个呢?
World's End by T.C. Boyl
T.C. Boyl的
That was a birthday gift... from my roommate.
那是生日礼物... 我室友送的
Haven't checked it o yet.
还没瞄过一眼呢
Oh. Oh, you should.It's-it's a good read.
噢 那应该看了 是本好书
Well, what about this? This is ridiculous.
还有这个呢? 真是神奇呀
You play bass?
你玩贝斯?
Seriously, ask my friends.I always say, my ideal woman...
说真的 问问我的朋友  我总是说 我理想中的伴侣...
does not play bass, because this is clearly yo roommate's.
是不玩贝斯的 ... 因为很明显这也是你室友的
- She's in a band. - : Damn, that's cool.
- 她跟人组了个乐队 - 可恶 太帅了
This is unbelievable.
真是难以置信
You st picked out the only three things in here that are my roommate's.
我室友只有三件物品在我房间 而你都选中了
- So, does your roommate's band ever play shows, or...? - Get out.
- 你那室友的乐队有没演出过...? - 出去
NARRATOR:  Kids, as you probably guessed,
孩子们 正如你们所想
that wasn't the night  I met your mother.
那晚我没和你们老妈见面
Although I think  I glimpsed her foot.
不过我想我有瞟到她的小脚脚
But I did get  a little bit closer to meeting the woman  of my dreams.
但我确实离我梦中情人更近了些
And your mom--
而你们母亲--
well,she got  her yellow umbrella back.
她的小黄伞回来了
It was just so ecial, you know?
那真的很特别
I feel like we should give him a moment of silence.
我们应该让他安静片刻
Followed by, like, 20 minutes of grunting.
然后在鬼混个20分钟
I'm gonna make you feelll better.
我会让你好起来的
- Let me just go freshen up. - All right.
- 我去洗把脸 - 好的
Oh, wait. No, no, that's not the bathroom!That...
等等 别 那不是洗手间! 那...
e these yours?
这都是你的?
I'm suit-sitting for someone
我是个看西装的
Barney, you lied to me.
Barney 你骗了我
You have to choose right now.
现在你必须选择了
Me... or theuits.
是我... 还是西装
* I know what you're thinkin', "What's Barney been drinkin'?" *
* 我知道你们在想什么 "Barney是不是喝多了? *
* That girl was smokin' hot!
* 那女孩辣的冒烟!*
* Yes, I coulda nailed her, but no, it's not a failure *
* 没错 我本可以上她  但不 这不是失败 *
* 'Cause there's one thing e is not *
* 因为她缺了一点 *
* To score a ten would be jusfine *
* 得分上垒固然不错 *
* But I'd rather be dressed to the nes *
* 但我却愿西装笔挺失一分 *
* It's a truth you can't refute *
* 这是事实 不能否认 *
* Nothin' suits me like a suit!
* 没有什么比西装更适合我!
* Picture a wor Where all the boys and girls are impeccably well-dressed! *
* 试想一个所有人都西装笔挺的世界! *
* That delive guy in a jacket and tie *
* 送货员穿着西装外套 带着领带 *
* That puppy in a double breast! *
* 那只狗也穿双排扣! *
* That eighties dude with muttonchops *
* 那留着络腮胡的半大小伙 *
* That baby with a lollipop!
* 那拿着棒棒糖的小男孩!
* That lady cop who's kinda cute *
* 那挺可爱的女警 *
* Nothing suits them like a suit! *
* 没有什么比西装更适合他们! *
* A wingman can wear!
* 泡妞搭子能穿! *
* They're, oh,  debonair
* 他们快乐自信 *
* The perfect way to snare a girl with daddy issues *
* 泡上有恋亲情结女生的必杀技 *
*n navy blue or black!
* 海军蓝或黑! *
* Check out this perfect rack
* 看着完美的架子 *
* I want to give them a squeeze *
* 真想挑逗一下 *
Oh, really!
真的吗!
* Then answer these questions
* 那就回答我 *
* If you please
* 这边请 *
* What would you do ifou had to choose *
* 一锅金子与你的西装 *
* Between your suits and a pot of gold? *
* 你会怎么选择? *
* Suits
* 西装 *
* What would you say if you gave your suits away And in return you'd never grow old? *
* 若放弃西装你便能长生呢? *
* Suit.* What would you pick: one million chicks *
* 西装* 一百万支票与简单的三件套 *
* Or a single three-piece suit?
* 你怎么选择? *
It's moo
* 真无聊 *
* What if world peace were within your reach? *
* 若世界和平掌握在你手呢? *
: I'm gonna stop you right there.
我打断一下
It's suits.Come on, Lily, get your head out of your ass.
当然是西装 Lily 想东西要用大脑
Two, three, four!
二 三 四!
* Girls will go and girlwill come *
* 妞们来来往往 *
* But there's only one absolute! *
* 但唯有一事长存! *
* Every bro on the go needs to know *
* 所有爷们必须记住 *
* That there's no accepted substitute! *
* 没有什么可替换! *
* I'm sry, Suits, let's make amends *
* 不好意思 西装 咱们改改吧 *
* My Sunday best are my best friends! *
* 节日盛装才是我的好朋友! *
* Send Caal Friday down the laundry chute *
* 周五的便装就让他去干洗店呆着吧 *
* 'Cause nothing suits the undisputed Oft-saluted  suitor of repute *
* 因为毫无争议的 *
* Like...
* 最适合所有老少爷们的 *
* A...
* 就是...*
Wa for it.
等等
* Suit...
* 西装... *
* Nothing suits him Like... a... *
* 他穿什么都不如... 穿上... *
*suit... Suit! Up!  Suit! Up! *
*西装... 穿上! 西装!  穿上! 西装! *
Then ain, she is pretty hot.
再重申一次 她真的很性感
I choose you, baby.
宝贝 我选择你 (cao...)
First thing tomorrow, I'm getting rid of these suits.
明天一早 我就扔掉这些西装
Really?
真的? 当然
放心 你们没事
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/=-
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品  本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径